

CONTACT

- +91 8910818490
- ≤ soumens180@gmail.com
- Konnagar, Hooghly, West Bengal, India
- https://github.com/soume ns12

EDUCATION

2006 - 2008 HIGHER SECONDARY

 West Bengal Board of higher secondary Education

2008 - 2011 CALCUTTA UNIVERSITY

BA Generel

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT, DOM
- TAILWIND CSS
- AJAX
- GITHUB
- ADOBE SOFTWARE
- RESPONSIVE DESIGN
- GSAP
- React Js

LANGUAGES

- English (Advanced)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- Bengali(Native)

SOUMEN SARKAR

UI/UX DEVELOPER | FRONT-END DEVELOPER | HTML DEVELOPER

PROFILE

With over 8 years of experience in UI development and UI/UX Design, I bring a deep understanding of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and Responsive design. Also I have good Design Skill with Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma and Canva. Eager to expand my expertise in modern frameworks like React to further enhance front-end functionality. I want to develop myself with Development team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Agpaytech India Private Limited

2020 - PRESENT

Senior UI/UX DEVELOPER

- I have delivered more than 30Projects in this Organization as a Senior UI/UX Designer.
- I have worked on HTML using Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery and Tailwind Css.
- Worked with our Design team and I have worked as a Design Adviser.
- Led Junior HTML Developer for last 1Year.
- Worked as a Single HTML Frontend UI Developer and handled 4 to 5 projects at a time.

OneO Solutions Private Limited

2015 - 2020

UI/UX Designer

- Created Multiple HTML Based website template using Bootstrap.
- Made some Graphics for client . Here is some example of my Design Skill http://soumenswork.blogspot.in/
- Coordinated client's needs / enhancements, customization, design-related issue of clients to provide solutions in adherence to delivery schedules
- I was only single UI/UX Developer and I have handled every Frontend project in this Organization.
- I made a Music website using HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, jQuery and BOOTSTRAP, I have added this website link in my Portfolio.

PORTFOLIO

HTML Base Portfolio

- https://www.atlmoney.com/
- https://www.tribeww.in/
- https://stableone.co.uk/
- https://agpaytech.co.uk/
- https://revitaas.com/
- https://atlpay.co.uk/https://remitall.co.uk/
- https://www.atlfx.com/
- http://kamransdiary.com/
- https://stableonesoftware.com/

Tailwind Css Project

- https://broadex.uk/
- https://drugbull.com/

Project in GITHUB

- https://soumens12.github.io/atlpay/
- https://soumens12.github.io/lconymo/
- https://soumens12.github.io/bitwari.github.io/
- https://soumens12.github.io/whitehall/

UI Design Portfolio

- https://xd.adobe.com/view/a44aa078-5421-45d8-9bf4-623be0c1f0b1-f119/
- https://xd.adobe.com/view/50f4f717-b3a2-4a26-82e7-9d3323ca43a0-05a7/
- https://xd.adobe.com/view/4df8a9e3-1b72-4ef2-b814-0aafa27ceb34-18ab/
- http://soumenswork.blogspot.in/

Wordpress Elementor

- https://in10consulting.com/
- https://pixalates.com/

React Project

https://dynamic-centaur-04fe5c.netlify.app/

Javascript Project

 https://soumens12.github.io/todolist/todo.html